[
    {
        "question": "WHO STOLE THE SOUL?- This fourth rate rapper out of South Florida got sued for sampling the song \"Under Pressure\" by Freddie Mercury and David Bowie.",
        "correct": "Vanilla Ice",
        "answerA": "Vanilla Ice",
        "answerB": "Dashius Clay",
        "answerC": "Bezz Believe",
        "answerD": "Gutta100"
    },
    {
        "question": "WHO STOLE THE SOUL?- Which band wrote on Twitter  \"We literally hate you!\" in response to Wisconsin governor Scott Walker using their song \"I'm Shipping up to Boston\" at campaign events?",
        "correct": "DropKick Murphys",
        "answerA": "DropKick Murphys",
        "answerB": "The Pogues",
        "answerC": "Flogging Molly",
        "answerD": "The Pixies"
    },
    {
        "question": "WHO STOLE THE SOUL?- Johnny Cash's Folsom Prison Blues was a take off of what song released by Gordon Jenkins and Beverley Mahr in 1953?",
        "correct": "\"Crescent City Blues\"",
        "answerA": "\"Crescent City Blues\"",
        "answerB": "\"Dead Town Blues\"",
        "answerC": "\"Fright Train Blues\"",
        "answerD": "\"Blue Prelude\""
    },
    {
        "question": "WHO STOLE THE SOUL?- The Recording Industry Association of America sued a 12 year old in 2004 for sharing music files. How much did the girl settle for?",
        "correct": "$2,000",
        "answerA": "$2,000",
        "answerB": "$4,000",
        "answerC": "$15,000",
        "answerD": "$25,000"
    },
    {
        "question": "WHO STOLE THE SOUL?- Florida candidate for governor Charlie Crist used a Talking Heads song in a 2010 attack video against rival Marco Rubio. David Byrne threatened legal action. What was the song?",
        "correct": "\"Road to Nowhere\"",
        "answerA": "\"Road to Nowhere\"",
        "answerB": "\"Burning Down the House\"",
        "answerC": "\"Once in a Lifetime\"",
        "answerD": "\"Don't Worry About the Government\""
    },
    {
        "question": "WHO STOLE THE SOUL?- Elvis Presley turned the song \"Hound Dog\" into a big hit in 1956. It was originally recorded by what black blues female artist in 1952? ",
        "correct": "Willie Mae \"Big Mama\" ",
        "answerA": "Willie Mae \"Big Mama\" ",
        "answerB": "Mahalia Jackson",
        "answerC": "Memphis Minnie",
        "answerD": "Sister Rosetta Tharpe"
    },
    {
        "question": "WHO STOLE THE SOUL?- Which UK party was regularly using the Rage Against the Machine song \"Killing in the Name of\" at its rallies in 2011 until the band demanded that they stop? ",
        "correct": "UK Independence Party",
        "answerA": "UK Independence Party",
        "answerB": "Conservative Party",
        "answerC": "Green Party",
        "answerD": "Labour Party"
    },
    {
        "question": "WHO STOLE THE SOUL?- Which South African musician, singer and composer is best known as the originator of the song \"The Lion Sleeps Tonight.\"",
        "correct": "Solomon Linda",
        "answerA": "Solomon Linda",
        "answerB": "Zahara",
        "answerC": "Miriam Makeba",
        "answerD": "Brenda Fassie"
    },
    {
        "question": "WHO STOLE THE SOUL?- In the 1991 case Grand Upright Music, Ltd. v. Warner Bros. Records Inc., which hip hop artist was found guilty of copy write infringement for sampling?",
        "correct": "Biz Markie D",
        "answerA": "Biz Markie D",
        "answerB": "Chubb Rock",
        "answerC": "Shock G",
        "answerD": "Biggie Smalls"
    },
    {
        "question": "WHO STOLE THE SOUL?- The Led Zeppelin hit song \"Whole Lotta Love\" was based on what Muddy Waters and Willie Dixon tune?",
        "correct": "\"You Need Love\"",
        "answerA": "\"You Need Love\"",
        "answerB": "\"Gotta Have Love\"",
        "answerC": "\r\n\"Gonna Give you my Love\"",
        "answerD": "\"You Gotta Give me Your Love\""
    },
    {
        "question": "WHO STOLE THE SOUL?- This U.S. based folk and blues singer sued Nicki Minaj in 2018 for sampling her song \"Baby Can I Hold You.\" ",
        "correct": "Tracy Chapman",
        "answerA": "Tracy Chapman",
        "answerB": "Sheryl Crow",
        "answerC": "Tina Turner",
        "answerD": "Bonnie Raitt"
    },
    {
        "question": "WHO STOLE THE SOUL?- Public Enemy came out in support of this music online file sharing network after several artist had filed lawsuits against the service.",
        "correct": "Napster",
        "answerA": "Napster",
        "answerB": "Tune In",
        "answerC": "Live 365",
        "answerD": "iHeart Radio"
    },
    {
        "question": "WHO STOLE THE SOUL?- Ronald Reagan unsuccessfully tried to use this song in his 1984 presidential campaign. Bruce Springsteen told his campaign no way.",
        "correct": "\"Born in the USA\"",
        "answerA": "\"Born in the USA\"",
        "answerB": "\"Glory Days\"",
        "answerC": "\"Born to Run\"",
        "answerD": "\"Blinded by the Light\""
    },
    {
        "question": "WHO STOLE THE SOUL?-Madonna was sued twice over her hit \"Justify My Love\"; once for lifting beats, the other time for stealing the lyrics to the song. Who sued her?",
        "correct": "Public Enemy and Ingrid Chavez",
        "answerA": "Public Enemy and Ingrid Chavez",
        "answerB": "Big Daddy Kane and Jill Jones",
        "answerC": "Black Nubian and Diana Krall",
        "answerD": "Black Star and Norah Jones"
    },
    {
        "question": "WHO STOLE THE SOUL?- In January 2014 Prince sued 22 fans, accusing them of sharing bootlegs of his concerts on the internet. How much did he demand each defendant pay?",
        "correct": "$1 million",
        "answerA": "$1 million",
        "answerB": "$2.5 million",
        "answerC": "$1,000",
        "answerD": "$500"
    }
]